== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)Thank you for your services,
gentlemen.
(Sheldon:)Now, I'm hoping
(Sheldon:)to broaden our audience
(Sheldon:)with your youthful
rock and roll music.
(Howard:)Aw,
(Howard:)you think you have
an audience, that's funny.
(Raj:)We don't get paid?
Nothing?
(Raj:)Not even a sandwich?
(Amy:)It's almost dinner time.
(Amy:)You in the mood for anything?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, we could get Thai food
near your apartment
(Sheldon:)and then drop in and
check on the progress.
(Amy:)Oh, you don't want do that,
it's a construction zone.
(Sheldon:)So?
(Amy:)Well, what about your fear of
stray nails and butt cracks?
(Sheldon:)I am terrified of
stepping on a nail
(Sheldon:)and falling into a butt crack.
(Amy:)Anyway, how about dinner?
(Sheldon:)You know, if
you'd like, I could
(Sheldon:)call your landlord and complain.
(Amy:)Thanks, but you don't have to.